No, the uniform looks good on you.
いや、制服似合うね
amazing.
すごい
Do you usually wear a uniform?
普段は制服?
Yes, it's a uniform that looks kind of similar.
はい、なんか似てるような感じの制服です
Ah, are they similar?
あ、似てる?
Yeah.
うん
Is it like this?
こんな感じなの?
Laser?
レーザー?
yes.
はい
Just bring it sometime.
ちょっと今度持ってきて
Can I stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってみていい?
Can I take a look behind you?
ちょっと後ろ見てみていい?
So, have you ever been killed?
じゃあ、倒殺されたこととかある?
No.
ないです
Oh, there isn't.
あ、 ないんだ
Do you always wear skirts this short?
こんな短いのいつもスカート?
yes.
はい
Then sit down again.
じゃあもう一度座ってみて
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's oney punny.
オニープニーじゃん
O kneepnee.
オ ニープニー
My hair is so smooth, really.
髪サラサラだよね、ほんとね
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
There's no need to touch it today.
今日触るの無しですよね
I just want to take pictures.
撮 るだけなんで
Just shoot today?
今日撮るだけ?
yes.
はい
It's okay to take pictures.
撮ってはいいんだよね
It's really smooth, isn't it?
ほんとすべすべだよね、ちょっと
A little salame.
ちょっとサラメで
No.
ダメです
picture?
え?
Today I'm just going to take pictures.
撮るだけなんで今日は
How far can I photograph?
どこまで撮っていいの?
I want a massage.
マッサージしたい
No, it's okay.
いや、大丈夫です
picture?
え?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Why why?
なんでなんで?
Why is the salame below?
サラメは下でなんで
Okay, I'll just add a little extra money.
ちょっとじゃあ、ちょっとだけ、 お金プラスするから、
Something like that over clothes.
ちょっと なんか、服の上からとか
A little more.
ちょいさらに
I'll help you.
助けてあげるからね
My hair is smooth, though.
髪サラサラだね、でも
What what?
なになに?
A little bit today.
今日ちょっと
picture?
え?
I heard you just take pictures?
撮るだけって聞いてたんですか?
No, no, no, no.
いやいや、違う違う
I thought it was amazing because my hair was so silky.
髪がタラタラだから、 すごいなって
I was wondering what kind of shampoo you use.
どんなシャンプー使ってるのかなって思って
What kind of shampoo do you use?
ど んなシャンプー使ってるの?
It's a normal shampoo.
普通のシャンプーのやつです
Let's hold hands.
手繋ごうじゃん
Hey, that's fine.
ね、それはいいしょ
Your hands are big.
手、おっきいね
Oh, it was tiny.
あ、ちっちゃかった
ERROR
えー、すごいね
You're young, after all.
若いよね、やっぱ
It's smooth.
すべすべだもんね
yeah?
ん?
what?
なに?
Just a little bit is fine.
ちょっとだけいいじゃん
Because it's a plus.
プラスするから
It's skinship.
スキンシップじゃん
Smooth, amazing.
すべすべ、すごい
all.
すべて
It's smooth.
すべすべだよ
Hey.
ねえ
what?
なに?
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Just for a little while.
ちょっとだけだから
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
You're in trouble for money right now.
お金困ってるでしょ、今
Hey, I'll help you out.
ちょっと、助けてあげるから
Just give me a massage.
マッサージだけさせて
ERROR
疲れてるでしょ?
Are you tired?
疲れてる?
Where are you tired?
どこ疲れてる?
shoulder.
肩
I don't know, shoulder.
わかんない、肩
shoulder.
肩
ERROR
肩は結構、成長期だから、この辺とか
Well, it seems like it would be good to rub it.
じゃあ、揉むといいらしい
It's okay, it's okay.
いいです、いいです
picture?
え?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
why?
なんで?
No?
だめ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
I'll just add a little bit here.
ちょっとプラスするから、ここだけ
Let me massage you.
マッサージさせて
yes.
はい
Ah, it's soft.
あ、柔らかいね
It's elaborate, I guess.
凝ってるね、やっぱね
It's elaborate, it's elaborate.
凝ってる、凝ってる
I understand.
わかるんだよ
It's soft.
柔らかいね
My legs are tired too.
足も疲れてるんだね
What what?
なになに?
Aren't you tired?
疲れてない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm not tired.
疲れてない
I'm tired.
疲れてるよ
I'll give you a massage.
マッサージしてあげるから
what?
なに?
No?
だめ?
No way, right?
だめだろ?
That's tough.
厳しいね
picture?
え?
copper?
どう?
massage.
マッサージ
it hurts.
痛い
it hurts?
痛い?
yes.
そう
But you were born, right?
でも、生まれたことあるでしょ?
do not have?
ない?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
It's so beautiful.
凄い綺麗だね
It's so beautiful and full.
凄い綺麗なっぱいだね
Really.
本当に
That's fine.
いいじゃん
why?
なんで?
Why not?
なんでダメなの?
no.
いや
Don't touch it too much.
触るのはあんまり
So beautiful
こんな綺麗な
...
I saw it.
見 ちゃった
I'll touch it a little.
ちょっと触っちゃうね
Awesome.
すっごい
Have you ever touched it?
触ったことあるでしょ?
do not have?
ない?
why?
なんで?
Yeah?
うん?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Then take a look.
じゃあ見てみて
copper?
どう?
It's delicious.
美味いじゃん
Do it with both feet.
両足でやって
It's delicious.
美味いじゃん
That's amazing.
凄いね
Isn't it okay to just take a look?
ちょっと見るでいいでしょ?
contents.
中身
Don't you want to see inside?
中、見たいくない?
I want to see it.
見たいじゃん
amazing.
凄い
So beautiful.
凄い綺麗
Yeah?
うん?
Did it seem like it was a bit crowded?
ちょっと溜めそうだった?
why?
なんで?
Don't sleep.
寝てんじゃん
why?
なんで?
Open your pussy a little.
ちょっとおまんこ開いてみて
Try opening it carefully.
しっかり開いてみて
Don't you know?
わかんない?
No.
ダメ
Just sleep.
寝てんじゃんだけ
Yeah.
うん
Just a little more.
もうちょい
Hey, can I get some sleep?
ねぇ、 ちょっと寝てもいい?
No, that's no good.
いや、 それダメでしょ
why?
なんで?
OF.
NG
Is it NG?
NGなの?
But it feels good.
でも気持ちいいじゃん
Right, just rub it.
でしょ、こするだけ
No.
ダメ
No, no, no.
ダメダメ
No?
ダメ?
I'll give you some money.
ちょっとお金あげるじゃん
Plus again.
プラスまた
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Really.
本当に
why?
なんで?
You do it all the time, right?
してるでしょ、いつもだって
No, no.
ダメです、ダメです